嘿
Hey.
早安 老虎
Good morning, tiger.
我在帮你准备丰盛的早餐 这样今晚你才有办法继续奋战
I'm making you a big breakfast, so you can keep up your strength for tonight.
你可要认真做 让我怀孕
You're gonna get me good and pregnant.
我今天早上竟然没事 我失业了
I've got nowhere to go this morning. I'm unemployed.
我不知道人生该怎么办才好
I don't know what I'm gonna do with my life.
嗯 我没有性趣了
Well, I just lost my erection.
不 我是认真的 我的人生该怎么办呢？
No, I mean, what am I supposed to do with myself?
你应该要找寻生命中的热情
You're supposed to find your passion in life.
你现在可以做任何你想要做的事 这是很刺激的
You can be whatever you want to be now. It's exciting.
是啊 但是这一切都太突然了 我不知道要如何开始
Yeah, but it's all so overwhelming. I don't know where to start.
等一下 我可以帮你
Hey, wait a second. I can help you with this.
你只要整理好就行了 我们可以列出你的资历
You just need to be organized. We can make a list of your qualifications...
然后将工作机会按照产业分类 我们可以用档案夹跟档案…
and categorize jobs by industry. There could be folders and files...
嘿 你超爱分类整理的偏执个性 可以派上用场了
Hey, this is where your hyper-organized pain-in-the-ass stuff pays off.
对啊
I know!
我又有性趣了！
My erection is back!
谢谢
Thank you.
乔伊 我可以喝一口你的咖啡 吃一口你的松饼吗？
Ooh, Joey, could I have a sip of your coffee and a bite of your muffin?
- 好的   - 谢谢你
- Okay.     - Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
菲比 你有没有 被饥饿的意大利人爱过？
Uh, Pheebs, have you ever been bitten by a hungry Italian?
很抱歉 只是我最近手头有点紧
I'm sorry. It's just, I'm a little short on cash.
如果你有需要 我可以借你一些钱
Oh, if you want, I could loan you some money.
喔 不 我已经得过教训 千万别跟朋友借钱
Oh, no, no, no. I learned never to borrow money from friends.
那就是为什么理查德不再跟我说话的原因
No. That's why Richard Dreyfuss and I don't speak anymore.
嘿 这样好了 要不要 来当我们电视剧的临时演员？
Ooh, hey, how about this? Wanna be an extra on my show?
- 可以吗？ - 可以啊
- You could do that?     - Yeah, yeah.
钱还不错 而且只要有需要就可以做
The pay's pretty good, and you could do it for as long as you need.
- 喔 我的天 我要上电视了   - 好了 现在…
- Oh, my God. I'm gonna be on TV!     - Okay, now...
我得告诉你 上电视并不像你想像的 那样光鲜亮丽跟好玩
I gotta tell you, being on TV isn't as glamorous and exciting as you think.
- 真的吗？ - 比你想的更棒
- Oh, really?     - No, it is awesome.
大家好
Hey, guys.
-嗨   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hi.
噢
Oh, wow.
你们为什么穿的这么正式？
Hey, why are you all dressed up?
我们要带艾玛去罗夫罗兰跟大家见面
We're bringing Emma to Ralph Lauren today to introduce her to everyone.
- 她看起来很可爱吧？ - 当然很可爱
- Doesn't she look cute?     - She sure does.
为什么她头上要贴 那个粉红色的蝴蝶结呢？
Why does she have a pink bow taped to her head?
因为如果再有人说"真是个可爱的小男生…"
If one more person says, "What a cute little boy"...
我会用车子的天线鞭打他们
I'm gonna whip them with a car antenna.
我想她会是办公室里面最时髦的
I think she's gonna be the hit of the office, huh?
是啊 她一定会比那些穿波希米亚上衣跟A字裙的漂亮多了
Yeah, she's gonna be hotter than, uh, peasant blouses and A-line skirts.
可以给我一个粉蓝色的蝴蝶结吗？
Can I get a blue bow?
好了 我看过很多就业情报…
Okay. I have looked through a bunch of career guides...
拷贝好并画线标示出重要讯息…
photocopied and highlighted key passages...
然后按字母分类归档 让你可以做出正确的决定
and put them into alphabetical folders, so you can make an informed decision.
我在里面多久了？
How long was I in there?
好了 我们先从A开始 广告
Okay, let's start with the A's. Advertising.
等一下 广告 这主意好棒
Wait. Advertising, that's a great idea.
你不想要再听别的了吗？
Well, don't you wanna look through the rest?
我想我不用听别的了 广告最适合了
I don't think I have to hear the rest. Advertising makes perfect sense.
很抱歉浪费你这么多时间
I'm sorry you had to waste all this time.
你认为跟标签机独处八小时 是浪费时间？
You call eight hours alone with my label maker wasted time?
现在可以用上我的碎纸机了
Ooh, now I'll get to use my shredder!
我可以创作广告口号 那能有多难？是不是？
I mean, I could write slogans. I mean, how hard could it be, right?
起司
Cheese.
是可以咀嚼的牛奶
It's milk that you chew."
"饼干 因为起司需要同伴"
"Crackers. Because your cheese needs a buddy."
"葡萄 因为整颗西瓜塞不进嘴里"
"A grape. Because who can get a watermelon in your mouth?"
我想到一个
Oh, I got one.
"袜子 因为你家人的脚 值得用最好的"
"Socks. Because your family's feet deserve the best."
亲爱的 让专业的人说好吗？
Honey, leave it to the pros.
我认识一个在广告业工作的人
I actually know someone in advertising.
我跟他从小玩到大 现在他是一家大广告公司的副总
I grew up with a guy who is a vice president at a big agency.
或许我可以请他跟你谈谈 电话给我
Maybe I can get him to meet you. Give me the phone.
"电话 让你跟有电话的人更贴近"
"The phone. Bringing you closer to people who have phones."
"婚姻 不是每个人都适合的"
"Marriage. It's not for everybody."
真不错 几乎大家都知道她是女的
That went well. Almost everybody knew that she was a girl.
是啊 在你揍了那个搞错的男的之后 大家很快就知道了
Yeah, after you punched that one guy who got it wrong, word spread.
我要进我的办公室拿点东西
I'm just gonna go in my office and pick up some stuff.
- 你是谁？ - 你是谁？
- Who the hell are you?     - Who the hell are you?
我是拥有这间 办公室的人
I'm the hell person whose office this is.
说的好 瑞秋
Good one, Rach.
我是盖文米丘 那个要接替你工作的人
I'm Gavin Mitchell, the person who's taking over your job.
什么？
Excuse me?
你的宝宝真可爱
Oh, your baby's so cute.
但是为什么要在男生头上 别个粉红色蝴蝶结呢？
But why would you put a pink bow on a boy?
嘿 乔伊 你看我
Hey, Joey. Look at me.
我是护士耶
I'm a nurse.
- 是啊 你是护士   - 哈哈
- Yes, you are.     - Ha, ha.
我想该是用海绵 帮我擦澡的时候了
I think it might be time for my sponge bath.
对不起 我太习惯泡临时演员了
Sorry, I'm just so used to hitting on the extras.
- 你会期待出场吗？ - 期待啊 但是我有点紧张
- So are you excited about your scene?     - Yeah, but I'm a little nervous.
放轻松 别紧张 他们可能只会要你站在后面
Oh, relax. Don't be. They'll probably just make you stand in the background.
- 很好   - 你 这里 过来 这里
- Good.     - You. Here, come here. Here.
拿着这个托盘 站在黄线这里 听到"开麦拉"就开始移动
Take this tray, stand on this yellow mark. You're gonna move on "action."
走去手术台那边 停在蓝线上 然后把托盘放下
Walk over to the operating table, stop on the blue mark and put the tray down.
别走太快
Don't walk too fast.
但是也别瞎混
But don't dawdle.
好的 现在是怎样呢？
Okay. Now, what?
开麦拉！
And, action!
- 卡 卡   - 我很抱歉
- Cut! Cut.     - I'm sorry.
- 我很抱歉 我只是有点紧张   - 那就别紧张
- I'm sorry. I'm just a little nervous.     - Yeah, well, don't be.
你这样讲还真有用
Okay, that helps.
开麦拉
And, action!
卡
Cut!
别担心 菲比 我通常也是要拍三次才行
Don't worry about it. It usually takes me three takes too.
好啦 八次
Ha-ha-ha. All right, eight.
预备…
And...
开麦拉！
action!
那你对于广告还有其他问题吗？
So do you have any other questions about advertising?
没有 但是让我表演一下 我的专长
No. No. But let me show you what I can do.
"贝果跟甜甜圈…
"Bagels and doughnuts.
任何心情都适合吃的圆圈圈"
Round food for every mood."
摩妮卡警告过我 你可能会这样做
Monica warned me you might do that.
我想我们公司 可能有个适合你的职务
I think we might have something for you at the agency.
- 真的吗？太好了   - 有个不支薪的实习职缺
- Really? That's great.     - It's an unpaid internship.
真好笑 当你说"不支薪"的时候 听起来好像是"不支薪"
That's funny. When you said "unpaid," it sounded like you said "unpaid."
别这样 摩妮卡有份很不错的工作
Come on, now. Monica has a good job.
又不是说你有小孩要养
It's not like you have a family to support.
事实上 我们正在努力做人 我认为摩妮卡应该不想延期
Actually, we're trying. I don't think Monica is gonna want to postpone it.
我们今晚应该要做爱的
We're supposed to have sex tonight.
事实上 现在她或许 就已经光着身体在家了
Actually, she's probably at home, naked right now.
如果没有人阻止我 我会一直说话
I tend to keep talking till somebody stops me.
- 我可以想像她在床上的样子…   - 停
- I can picture her on the bed.     - Stop!
好的
Okay.
等等 你是什么意思 要接替我的工作？
Wait. What do you mean, you're taking over my job?
当你去度你的育婴假期时 你的工作是我在做的
Well, while you were on your baby vacation, I was doing your job.
假期？我对假期的定义可不包含…
A vacation? My idea of a vacation does not involve...
让什么东西吸我的乳头吸到破皮
something sucking on my nipples until they are raw.
你应该从未去过天体营渡假小岛
Clearly, you've never been to Sandals Paradise Island.
好 别太享受 因为我两个星期之后就回来了
All right. Don't get too comfortable there, because I'm back in two weeks.
我要一切回归原状
I want everything back the way it was.
我实在不太满意 你重新摆设我办公室的方式
I can't say I care too much for the way you've rearranged my office.
我实在不太满意 你带进来的那股味道
I can't say I care too much for that smell you've brought in.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
瑞秋 我们有个棕色警戒状况
Uh, Rach, uh, we have a code brown situation.
亲爱的 可以拜托你 帮我处理一下吗？
Honey, could you please take care of it for me?
好吧 但是有时候 你也该自己处理一次
All right, but you're gonna have to do one sometime.
让我把话说清楚
Let me just get this straight.
我去生个小孩 他们就派人过来接我的工作？
So I go have a baby, and they send some guy in to do my job?
嗯 本来有说 要关闭整家罗夫罗兰的
Well, there was talk of shutting down Ralph Lauren altogether.
好了 你真是个不要脸的临时工
Okay. Right. You're very cheeky for a temp.
我不是临时工 我是从别的部门调过来的
I'm not a temp. I was transferred here from another department.
是什么部门？浑蛋部门吗？
Oh, and what department was that? The, uh, jerk department?
他们并没有告诉我 你反应如此之快
They didn't tell me about your quick wit.
那他们也没有告诉你 我是橡皮擦 你是胶水吗？
Well, did they mention that I'm rubber and you're glue?
- 盖文 罗夫很喜欢你的创意   - 嗨 塞纳先生
- Gavin, Ralph loved your ideas.     - Oh, hi, Mr. Zelner.
瑞秋 我想你见过盖文了
Ah, Rachel. I see you've met Gavin.
你离开的时候 我们都不知道该怎么办
When you left us, we weren't sure what we were gonna do.
但是 盖文拯救了我们 超级盖文
But then, Gavin to the rescue. Super Gavin. Ha-ha-ha.
喔 太好了
Well, that's great.
那么 超级盖文 我回来以后…
So now, uh, Super Gavin, when I come back...
你计划要飞到哪儿去呢？
uh, where do you plan on flying off to?
全看塞纳先生的意思 我相信他会做出正确的决定
That's up to Mr. Zelner. I'm sure he'll make the right decision.
超级马屁精
Oh, wow. Super ass-kissing power.
对了 你什么时候要回来呢？
Incidentally, when, uh, are you coming back?
今天
Uh, today.
- 你刚刚不是说两星期后？ - 不 我是说今天
- You said two weeks.     - No, I said today.
看吧 身为超级英雄 听话能力也不怎么样
See, for a superhero, not so much with the listening.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
那他怎么说？
So, what'd he say?
嗯
Uh...
他有时候有点粗鲁…
He can be a little rough around the edges...
所以我要"小狗" 代换掉他常用的一个字眼
so I'm gonna replace a word he used a lot with the word "puppy."
他说"如果你的小狗朋友 不把小狗的角色演好…
Okay? So he said, "If your puppy friend doesn't get her puppy act together...
我会小狗的开除她"
I am gonna fire her mother-puppy ass."
很抱歉 我办不到 我不是演员的料
I'm sorry. I can't do this. I'm just not an actor.
没错 你不是演员 你是护士
That's right. You're not. You're a nurse.
- 你是拿托盘的护士   - 不 乔伊…
- You're Nurse With Tray.     - Joey...
拿托盘的护士不认识乔伊 她没有时间交朋友
Nurse With Tray doesn't know Joey. She has no time for friends.
她进去手术室把托盘交给医生…
She gets in that operating room and she carries that tray to the doctor...
因为如果她不这样做 有人会死的
because if she doesn't, people die.
谁会死？
Who dies?
戴眼罩的男人！
Man With Eye Patch!
现在你过去做好你的工作
Now, you get in there, and you do your job.
- 是的 医师   - 很好
- Yes, doctor.     - Okay.
好了 我们再试一次
Okay, let's try this one more time.
撑着点 戴眼罩的男人 你的托盘来了
Hang in there, Man With Eye Patch. Your tray is coming.
开麦拉
And, action.
太好了 我办到了 我搞定了
Yes, I did it! I nailed it!
喔
Whoo!
接下来是什么呢？
What's next?
是后面的剧情
The rest of the scene.
好的 大家 从头开始
Okay, from the top, people.
听着 计划改变 我的产假要结束了
Listen, sudden change of plans. Um, my maternity leave just ended.
他们说如果我不今天回去工作 他们就要开除我
They said if I didn't come back today, they'd fire me.
什么？那样是非法的
What? No, that's illegal.
我要马上通知劳委会 他们不…
I'll have the Labor Department here so fast, they won't...
好了 冷静点 诺玛 他们并没有真的那样说
All right, calm down, Norma Rae. They didn't actually say that.
我只是害怕如果不现在回去 那个男的会把我挤掉
I'm just afraid if I don't come back now, this guy will try and squeeze me out.
那艾玛怎么办？ 我们还没有找到保姆
But what about Emma? I mean, we don't have a nanny.
我知道 我们只好今晚再想办法了
I know. We're just gonna have to figure out a plan tonight.
你今天可以先照顾她吗？
Can you please just take care of her for today?
当然 只要你的胸部给我 我们马上就走
Absolutely. Just give me your breasts, and we'll be on our way.
别这样 我不知道还能怎么办
Come on. I don't know what else to do.
- 好啦 好啦   - 好
- Fine. Fine.     - Okay.
我们开心的 对不对？对 会很开心的 对 我们…
We'll have fun, won't we? Yes, we will. Yes, we...
- 罗斯   - 嗯？
- Ross.     - Huh?
你好漂亮
You're pretty.
不管我决定要做什么 都得从基层做起
Whatever I decide to do, I'm gonna be starting a new career from scratch.
要一阵子我才有办法真正赚些钱
It's gonna be a while before I make a living at it.
或许现在不是生小孩的好时机
Maybe now's not the right time to be starting a family.
所以你要跟摩妮卡说 你现在不想要生小孩？
So you have to tell Monica you don't want to have a baby right now?
是啊
Yeah.
再见了
Goodbye.
好了 生小孩时间  裤子脱掉 宾
Okay, it's baby time. Pants off, Bing.
没看到你也在 盖勒
Didn't see you there, Geller.
罗斯在这里 所以…
Yeah, Ross is here, so...
是啊是啊
Uh, yeah, uh-huh. Yeah.
我还在想 可以在你们这里混一下
Uh, and I was really hoping that maybe I could hang out.
- 嗯   - 你们想要做什么呢？
- Mm.     - What do you, uh, feel like doing?
我们想要做爱
Well, uh, we're gonna have sex.
我倒是不太想做爱
I don't feel like having sex.
或许…我不知道
Uh, maybe, uh... I don't know.
或许我们可以一起看电影什么的
Maybe we can watch a movie or something.
我这样说好了
Uh, let me put it this way:
不管你在不在 我们都要做爱
We're having sex whether you're here or not.
裤子脱掉 宾
Pants off, Bing.
现在既然我回来了 何不告诉我你做了什么
Now that I'm back, why don't you just fill me in on what you've been up to?
嗯 我把你《F4》的屏幕保护程式改了
Well, I've changed your screen saver from that picture of *NSYNC.
嘿 我离开时 他们可是很受欢迎的
Hey, they were popular when I left.
我在准备明天一个很重要的报告
I'm working on this big presentation for tomorrow.
我应该要参与的 跟我说明吧
I should be involved in that, so get me up to speed.
那会花上好几个星期 让我处理这个报告就可以了
That'll take weeks. Let me take care of the presentation.
不 我知道 你在玩什么花样 好吗？
Oh, no. I see what you're doing here, all right?
这是我的工作 我已经做了五年 我知道一切流程
This is my job, buddy. I've had it for five years, and I know how it works.
- 所以赶快跟我解释   - 好
- So why don't you just catch me up?     - Fine.
天啊 你把我椅背的角度完全变了
Oh, God. You've totally messed with the back support on my chair.
- 你是怎么弄的？ - 你已经在这里五年了
- How do you fix this?     - You've been here five years.
- 你自己想   - 很好 我自己来
- You figure it out.     - Fine, I will.
好了 跟我说吧
All right, fill me in.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你有没有蓝色的领带跟这件配？ 艾玛吐奶到我的领带上
Do you have a blue tie that would go with this? Emma spit up on mine.
有啊 但是我找到工作时要还我
Oh, yeah, but you have to give it back if I get a job.
当然 到那时候 领带已经被淘汰了…
Of course, by that time, ties will be obsolete...
而我们全都穿银色的连身装
and we'll all be wearing silver jumpsuits.
- 早安 爱人   - 早安
- Hey, good morning, lover.     - Hey.
我得说 经过昨晚之后 我的双腿还在发软
I gotta say, after last night, I'm a little weak in the knees.
麻烦你 每次走进来的时候 先快速看一下四周吧
Here's an idea. You walk into a room, take a quick scan.
抱歉
Sorry.
但是我有点觉得 我们昨晚做人成功了
But I kind of have this feeling that we may have made a baby last night.
喔 天 我得告诉你一件事
Oh, God, I have to tell you something.
你没有怀孕
You're not pregnant.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
嗯 那件能使你怀孕的事？
Well, that thing that I have to do to make a baby?
我装的
I faked it.
什么？你装的？
What? You faked it?
你知道吗？
You know what?
我不需要领带了
I don't need a tie.
说真的 比较好 领子闻着 不是吗？
I mean, it's... It's better open collar, you know?
比较轻松自在
It's, uh, ahem, it's more casual.
乔伊 听着 我办不到 这实在不合常理
Joey. Listen, I can't do this. It doesn't make any sense.
昨天我是护士 今天我是服务生？
Yesterday I was a nurse, and today I'm a waitress at a café?
有时候我们会用相同的临时演员 扮演不同的角色 没关系的
Oh, sometimes we use the same extras for different parts. It's okay.
有关系 因为昨天我扮演护士 演出让人印象深刻
Well, it's not okay, because I gave a very memorable performance as the nurse.
现在突然间我变成服务生？ 我的影迷会混淆的
And now, suddenly, I'm the waitress? That's gonna confuse my fans.
嗯
Um, um...
嗯 或许你是护士…
Well, maybe you are a nurse...
但是你晚上兼差当服务生
but you moonlight as a waitress.
哦
Oh.
嗯
Uh-huh.
因为我是抚养两个小孩的单亲妈妈
Because I'm a single mother supporting my two children.
- 没错   - 对啊
- Nice. Yeah.     - Yeah.
等一下
Okay. Wait a minute.
德瑞克雷莫瑞医生跟我在同间医院工作 我不用过来打招呼吗？
Dr. Drake Ramoray and I work at the same hospital. Wouldn't I come say hi?
不 不 你跟德瑞克在吵架
No. No, see, uh, you and Drake are having a fight.
吵什么？
About what?
他跟你上床 然后再也没有打电话给你
He slept with you and then never called you.
而我只想帮 大卫跟贝琪找个新爸爸
And I just wanted a new daddy for Davey and Becky.
好了
Okay.
好了 好了 从头开始
Okay. Okay, from the top.
开麦拉
And, action.
我很讶异你会同意 跟我出来吃午餐
So I'm surprised you agreed to have lunch with me.
我也很讶异 但我终究是来了
I'm surprised too. But yet, here I am.
卡 卡
Cut! Cut!
你是在做什么？
What...? What are you doing?
我很气他 因为他跟我上过床之后 就再也没有打电话给我了
I'm very angry at him because he slept with me and never called me back.
- 我也是   - 还有我
- Me too.     - Me too!
冷静点 她是说在剧情里面
Oh, calm down. She means on the show.
我们需要新的临时演员
We need some new extras around here.
哇 你已经到了
Wow. You're here already.
是的 艾玛跟我 提早进来做研究 准备报告
Yes. Emma and I came in a little early to do research on the presentation.
事实上 我做了一些修改 我想我都准备好了
Actually, I made a few changes. I think I'm caught up on everything.
随便问我一个问题吧
So ask me anything.
- 你要怎么调整椅子呢？ - 除了这个
- How do you fix the chair?     - Ugh, except that!
哈罗 塞纳先生 今天下午的报告 我们都已经准备好了
Oh, hello, Mr. Zelner. We are all ready for our presentation this afternoon.
很好 因为十分钟之后就要开始了
Good, because it's in 10 minutes.
什么？我没办法 我宝宝在这里
What? I can't do that. I have the baby.
罗斯一个小时之后才会来接她
Ross is not gonna pick her up for an hour.
那盖文可以上台报告 我们现在就要开始了
Then Gavin can give the presentation. We have to do it now.
罗夫今天要提早走 他要去买直升机
Ralph needs to leave early today. He's going helicopter shopping. Heh.
好吧 满你的意了 你赢了 你赢了
Well, there you go, you win. You win.
你可以上台报告 让他们爱死你
You get to do the presentation. You'll knock them dead.
没有人会记得我在这里工作过 然后罗夫会买到直升机…
No one will remember that I worked here, and then Ralph will buy his helicopter...
超级盖文会跟他一起飞
and Super Gavin will just fly right alongside of him.
- 你可以上台去报告   - 不 我不行 我宝宝在这里
- You can do the presentation.     - No, I can't. I have a baby.
我会看着她
I'll watch her.
你为什么要这样？
Why would you do that?
因为你工作很辛苦 而这是你的工作 还有你有点疯狂
Because you worked really hard, and it's your job. And you're a little crazy.
你人真好
[VOICE BREAKING] That's really nice.
我应该告诉你 哭泣的女人让我觉得很不自在
I should tell you that crying women make me very uncomfortable.
嗯 那你可能不会喜欢 接下来要发生的事
Well, you're not gonna like what's coming.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉 我很抱歉 我很抱歉
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
天哪
God.
谢谢你 谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you.
嗯
Um.
好吧
Okay.
我没事的 别担心 我很会带小孩
I'm really fine. Don't worry. I'm great with children.
好吧
Okay.
我是盖文米丘 很高兴认识你
Gavin Mitchell. Pleased to meet you.
请不要开除我的朋友 让我先跟她谈谈
Please don't fire my friend. Just let me talk to her.
- 好吧 但这是她最后一次机会   - 谢谢 谢谢你
- Okay, but this is her last chance.     - Thank you.
我帮你一个忙如何？
How about I do something for you?
明天 我帮你带一顶帽子 让你遮住秃头
Tomorrow, uh, I'll bring you a hat, cover up the bald.
听着菲比 我刚跟导演谈完…
Hey, uh, listen, Pheebs. I was just talking to the director...
他说这一次你不要打德瑞克
and he was thinking maybe this time you don't hit Drake.
你只要端盘子就可以了
You just wait on the tables.
我不能那样做 我是演员 我有我的程序
I can't do that. I'm an actor. I have a process.
你是按摩师 你有的是挖了个洞的桌子
You're a masseuse. You have a table with a hole in it.
等等 我知道这是怎么回事了 你感到威胁了
Wait, I see what's happening here. You're threatened.
什么？
What?
我的演技好到抢了你的锋头
I'm so good in the scene that I'm stealing focus from you.
接受挑战吧 崔比亚尼 因为我只会提高你的水准
Well, rise to the challenge, Tribbiani, because I just raised the bar.
- 提升自己 向我看齐吧   - 哈哈
- Come join me up here.     - Ha-ha-ha.
你可以开除她 但是最好叫保全过来 请神容易送神难哦
Yeah, you can fire her, but I would call security. She won't go easy.
你装的？你不可能装的
You faked it? You couldn't have faked it.
当然可以 只要装点表情跟声音
Yes, you can. You just make the faces and the noises.
男生可以装吗？
Guys can fake it?
不可思议 这明明是女生的专长
Ugh, unbelievable. The one thing that's ours.
为什么在我们想要生小孩的时候 你要假装呢？
Why would you fake it when we're trying to have a baby?
嗯 这正是我要装的原因
Well, that's actually why.
听着 我正在换工作
Look, I'm starting a whole new career now.
我不是说我不想要孩子
I'm not saying I don't want a baby.
只是或许我们可以等一阵子
I'm just saying maybe we could wait a little while.
一个月吗？
Like...? Like a month?
- 或是一年？ - 真的吗？你想要等一年？
- Or a year?     - Really? You wanna wait a year?
应该不用到一年 你知道我的能力
It could be less than a year. I mean, you've heard my stuff.
"长裤 跟短裤一样 只是长一点"
"Pants. Like shorts but longer."
可能不只一年吧
It'll probably be more than a year.
我…
Wow. I...
- 我真的很想要生小孩   - 是啊 我也很想
- I really wanna have a baby.     - Well, yeah, me too.
这样好了 我回去做老本行好了
Look, I'll just get my old job back.
不 我要你做你热爱的工作
No, I want you to have a job that you love...
不是什么数据分析跟资料重组的
not statistical analysis and data reconfiguration.
我辞职后 你才了解我在做什么？
I quit, and you learn what I do?
我想 永远不会有 适合生小孩的时机
I think there's never gonna be a right time to have a baby.
现在你失业了 但过了一阵子…
Now you're unemployed, and in a little while...
你就会找到一份让你忙不过来的工作
you'll find a new job that'll keep you really busy.
总是会有理由不能生小孩的
There's always gonna be a reason not to do this...
但是我想 一旦有了宝宝 我们就会忘了所有的理由
but I think once the baby comes, we'll forget about all those reasons.
我想也是
I guess.
我是说 有小孩一直是很吓人的事
I mean, it's always gonna be scary when we have a baby.
真的会很吓人
It's gonna be really scary.
有小孩的时候…
I mean, God, when we have a baby...
会有许多事情是我们无法控制的
there's gonna be so much that we're not able to control.
我是说 这间公寓会是一团乱
I mean, the apartment's gonna be a mess.
我会没有时间 整理
I won't have time to clean it.
要是宝宝跑到缎带抽屉里…
What if the baby gets into the ribbon drawer...
把所有的缎带都弄乱了呢？
and messes up all the ribbons?
万一没有地方可以放缎带…
What if there's no room for a ribbon drawer...
因为所有的空间  都被宝宝的东西占满了呢？
because the baby's stuff takes up all the space?
缎带要放哪儿？
Where will all the ribbons go?
我们该不该在你改变主意之前 赶快去做人？
Should we go make a baby before you change your mind?
- 当然 拜托快点   - 好的
- Yes, please!     - Okay.
而且我保证 这一次我不会装了
Oh, and I promise I will not fake it this time.
真希望我也可以说相同的话 我现在有点激动
Well, I wish I could say the same. I'm a little shook up.
我知道你故意让手术失败
I know you botched that operation on purpose.
我还没有办法证明 等我可以证明 你会因谋杀而坐牢的
I can't prove it yet, but when I do, you'll be going to jail for murder.
我不在乎你是不是我弟弟
I don't care if you are my brother.
我不是你弟弟
I'm not your brother.
我的孩子怎么办呢？德瑞克！
What about my children, Drake? Huh?
不 不 不
No! No! No!
不 不
No! No!
天啊
God!